allpages.com 2019-10-31

# AllPages.com - Privacy Statement

### Privacy Policy

We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. AllPages.com provides online yellow pages listings. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the Web site, AllPages.com. 

We collect no personal information about you when you visit our web site unless otherwise stated or unless you choose to provide this information to us via the contact/feedback form or email. All personal information you provide on this site is kept confidential. 

However, we may collect and store certain information automatically. This information will not be shared with anyone beyond the web site support staff, except when required by law enforcement investigation, and will be used only as a source of anonymous statistical information. This information may include:  
• Internet Protocol (IP) address of the domain from which you access the Internet, either your individual address or the proxy provided by your Internet Service Provider (ISP).   
• Date and time you access our site.   
• Pages you view (recorded by the text and graphics files that compose that page).   
• Web address of the site from which you linked directly to our site.   
• Browser version and operating system of the computer you are using. 

We may use the summary statistics to help us make our site more useful to visitors, such as assessing what information is of most and least interest to visitors, and for other purposes such as determining the site�s technical design specifications and identifying system performance or problem areas. 

##### Cookies

Cookies are minute pieces of information that your browser stores on your hard drive. Cookies help everyone in that they help to make navigation around the site more swift, and prevent you from having to enter certain information that you have already given us each time you visit the site. Cookies help us to see how visitors use us, and when. They help us to discover which parts of our site are popular and which are not. We use cookies to assist with our site development. Most browsers these days are set up to automatically accept cookies. You may choose to provide us with personal information, by sending e-mail with questions or comments or by filling out an online form and submitting it to us through our web site. We use this information to  
•Gather the requested information.  
• Respond to Your message.  
• Follow-up as appropriate.

We do not create individual profiles with the information you provide. If information is collected, it will be used solely in connection with AllPages.com or for such other purposes as are described at the point of collection. We do not give, sell, or transfer any personal information to a third party.

However, your e-mail message, question, or comment may be forwarded to other AllPages.com employees, contractors or subcontractors, who may be better able to help you. Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, we do not share our e-mail with any other outside organizations. However, e-mail and on-line forms are not secure against interception and senders cannot expect privacy. 

We reserve the right, and you authorize us, to use and assign all information regarding our site uses by you and all information provided by you in any manner consistent with this section. AllPages.com may modify, alter, amend, modify, or otherwise fundamentally change its privacy policy at its sole discretion without prior notice to you by posting a change to its privacy policy on the site or by altering this agreement and posting it to the site. 

##### Links to other Sites

AllPages.com contains links to web sites operated by other parties. The links are provided for your convenience only. We do not control such web sites and are not responsible for the content and performance of these sites or for your transactions with them. Inclusion of links to such web sites does not imply any endorsement of the material on such web sites or any association with their operators. 

##### Advertisements on our Site

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us by accessing the Contact Us form.
